filmigallery.com 2013-05-13

# Fropki.org Privacy Policy - Filmi Gallery

Wow, you are interested. We hope the following information can help answer any questions you might have. And if you still want to know more, please drop us a line by clicking [here](http://www.filmigallery.com/contact.php)

The following Privacy Statement discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for FilmiGallery.com's Network of Web sites (which we collectively refer to below as the "Site"). 

Our Site, like most other sites, uses cookies to provide you with a more personalized and user-friendly experience. A cookie is a message that is sent to a browser from a Web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. Cookies help us keep track of the size of our audience, the frequency of visits to our Site and the areas that are most popular. If a guest makes a purchase, cookies are used to keep the shopping cart active during the shopping process. We may also use cookies to help us deliver content or advertising specific to your interests, and to save your preferences or passwords so you don't have to re-enter them each time you visit our Site. Most browsers allow you to reject all cookies, but then your preferences, passwords and other information will not be saved, and you may have to re-enter information to use certain features of our Site. 

We may use an outside ad company to display ads on our Site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies delivered through banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information. FilmiGallery.com may also serve banner ads that contain cookies. We will only share such information with our advertisers and sponsors on an aggregate basis to determine the success of any given banner, logo or advertisement. 

We may also log IP addresses for the purposes of systems administration or to report information in aggregate form to our advertisers (e.g., how many visitors logged in to our Web site). In some cases your IP address stays the same from browser session to browser session; but if you use a consumer Internet access provider such as AOL or Earthlink or Satyam, chances are that your IP address varies each session-thus making it effectively impossible for us to use your IP address (by itself) to determine who you are. 

In general, we will not disclose your personal information to third parties except to the extent necessary to provide you with a requested service, or under circumstances required by law. We will disclose your personal information when we believe in good faith that any applicable law, regulation, or legal process requires it, or where we believe disclosure is necessary to protect or enforce our rights or the rights of another user. We also disclose aggregated user statistics in order to describe our services and reach to prospective partners, advertisers, and other third parties. However, aggregate data is not traceable to you specifically. We may use contractors to help us with our operations. Some or all of these contractors may access our databases of user information. These contractors will enter into an agreement with us that places restrictive provisions on their use and disclosure of all information they obtain through the relationship. 

Specific uses of personal information that vary from this Privacy Statement (if any) may be found in the policies applicable to the service or feature you are signing up for. To the extent that you are notified of uses of your personal information that are different from those described in this Privacy Statement during your enrollment in any particular service, special program, contest or promotion, those uses will govern. For example, if you purchase a T-shirt from a specific celebrity fan site, that celebrity may be entitled to receive and use your personal information for limited purposes such as e-mailing you information about their next film or television appearance. Please be on the look-out for additional terms of service and privacy statements applicable to the services for which you sign-up or participate in. 

The Site contains links and advertisements to other sites. If you click-through a banner ad or link and submit your information to that advertiser or site, you will be subject to their own privacy practices. FilmiGallery.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other sites. 

The Site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and that if you disclose personal contact information in these areas, others may use it to send you unsolicited messages. We do not control the actions of our guests and registered members. FilmiGallery.com encourages our users to be smart about choosing when, and to whom to release information online.

Of course there are many other ways we conceivably could get information from or about you that are not described elsewhere in this Statement. For example, you might email us through one of our customer service email addresses, or we may get a complaint about you from a third party. Our practices with respect to such information are pretty much as you'd expect -- we use and disclose this information in a commercially reasonable business manner. 

This site has industry consistent security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. But since the Internet cannot be made absolutely secure, FilmiGallery.com assumes no liability for disclosure of data due to errors in transmission or unauthorized third parties. 

If you are a minor under 12, you are prohibited from submitting any personal information to us. 

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving promotional/marketing information from FilmiGallery.com and our partners. We also provide instructions for how to unsubscribe to future mailings at the bottom of each communication. Please remember to check the registration screens applicable to the service or promotion for which you are signing up for specific instructions from our partners on how to update your user profile and/or opt out of receiving offers and mailings.

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can [contact us.](http://www.filmigallery.com/contact.php)

By using the Site, you signify your acceptance of this Privacy Statement. If you are not comfortable with any policy described in this Privacy Statement, you may feel free to e-mail us with questions or concerns, but your only remedy is to discontinue use of the Site. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Statement at any time. 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, **[click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)**. 

You can also visit [www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser.
